highdots.com 2011-06-30

# Privacy Policy « OverZone Software

At OverZone Software we respect your privacy.

While visiting our web site, or using our software, we will not collect any personal information without your permission.  
We will not send you any unsolicited information, including email, except where you authorize us to do so.

Any information you provide to us will remain confidential to OverZone Software.

OverZone Software collects and uses information as follows: 

  * **Registration Information** : This is the information that you provide to us for product registration.
  * **Credit Card Information** : OverZone Software uses SWREG, Inc. a third-party provider of e-commerce solutions, and back-end facilitator to process your credit card information. Your credit card information does not pass through the OverZone Software Site. SWREG keeps your credit card information confidential and protects your credit card information through the use of industry-standard Secure Sockets (SSL) encryption technology. [Click here](https://usd.swreg.org/privacy.htm) to read the SWREG Privacy Statement.

Upon request we provide our customers with access to all information, including proprietary information that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. 

Customers can access this information by [contacting us](https://www.highdots.com/zone/submitticket.php).

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Our site does contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please [write to us](https://www.highdots.com/zone/submitticket.php).
